The fastest growth periods are often the most miserable.
If you want to progress, get used to pain.
If you think about what actually occurs when you grow,
you stretch past your point of comfort.
So even if you're growing a muscle,
like you stretch it, you break it down, it's painful.
If you have growing pains, like as a kid,
it's like you grew too fast
and your joints are in a lot of pain.
If you're a company and you expand,
this is technically supposed to be good stuff,
but it doesn't make it any less painful.
Elite athletes don't get stronger during easy workouts.
If we want progress,
we must accept the price of pain that's attached to it.
You cannot both want progress and live an easy life.
These two things conflict.